Register of the Jay Lovestone papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, 1917-1985 (Boxes 712-725)
  - "Post-Vietnam Asia," typescript, 1975 June 24 (Folder 720: 49)
  - Speech, AFL-CIO Labor Study Center, incomplete outline notes, 1975 July 22 (Folder 720: 50)
  - Notes re Eurocommunism, circa 1975 November (Folder 720: 51)
  - "The Hegemonic Class," holograph and typescript, circa 1976 (Box-folder 721: 1)
  - Notes re Eurocommunism, circa 1976 (Folder 721: 2)
  - "Soviet Explanation and Justification of New CPI, CPF., etc. Strategy," holograph, circa 1976 (Folder 721: 3)
  - "Justification and Support of PCI-PCF Course," holograph and typescript, circa 1976 March (Folder 721: 4)
  - "PCI: Solid with CPSU Internationalism," typescript, circa 1976 March (Folder 721: 5)
  - "Nearer My Heart to Thee: PCI Love Russia First," typescript, circa 1976 April (Folder 721: 6)
  - Speech, American Institute for Free Labor Development meeting, outline notes, 1976 April 20 (Folder 721: 7)
  - "Communists Will Not Defend Italy if Soviet Bloc Attacks Her," typescript, circa 1976 May (Folder 721: 8)
  - Interview by Archie Robinson, typed transcript, 1976 September 16 (Folder 721: 9)
  - "Comments on State Department Memorandum 'Down-Grading the Soviet Trade Unions?,'" typescript, 1976 October 13 (Folder 721: 10)
    Includes text of State Department memorandum.
  - Interview by Archie Robinson, typed transcript, 1976 October 15 (Folder 721: 11)
  - "Notes for Meeting...on 'The U.S. and China after Mao,'" holograph and typescript, 1976 November 30 (Folder 721: 12)
  - "Keys to Leninist (Communist) Strategy," holograph and typescript, 1977 (Folder 721: 13)
  - Memorandum re Harold Brown, typescript, 1977 (Folder 721: 14)
  - Memorandum re world situation, holograph and typescript, 1977 (Folder 721: 15)
  - "Soviet Inflation," notes, circa 1977 January (Folder 721: 16)
  - "Turbulent Flux and Polarization," holograph and typescript, 1977 February (Folder 721: 17)
  - International report to International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union General Executive Board, outline notes, 1977 February 11 (Folder 721: 18)
  - "Notes on President Carter's Address at the Notre Dame Commencement Exercises, South Bend, Indiana, May 22, 1977," typescript, circa 1977 May (Folder 721: 19)
  - "'Euro-Communism': Roots and Reality," Journal of International Relations, 1977 Summer
    - Notes and fragments (Folder 721: 20-22)
    - Preliminary drafts, holograph and typescript (Folder 721: 23)
    - Final draft, typescript (Box-folder 722: 1)
    - Printed copies (Folder 722: 2)
      Includes Journal of International Relations and AFL-CIO Free Trade Union News reprints, and pamphlet reprints in English, French, German, Italian, Portuguese and Spanish.
  - "The Ides of March, 1978," outline notes and typescript, 1977 September 21 (Folder 722: 3)
  - "Free World Labor Conference for Jobs and Security,", 1977 November 1 (Folder 722: 4)
    Notes, holograph, and typescript.
  - International report to International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union General Executive Board, notes and holograph, 1978 (Folder 722: 5)
  - "Relations Worsen between Jusos and SPD Leadership," typescript, circa 1978 (Folder 722: 6)
  - Report on international resolutions submitted to International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union convention, holograph and typescript, circa 1978 (Folder 722: 7)
  - "DGB Youth Undermined by Communists," typescript, circa 1978 January (Folder 722: 8)
  - Draft speech for Sol C. Chaikin in Egypt, typescript, 1978 January 15 (Folder 722: 9)
  - "Georg Leber's Resignation as Defense Minister of the Federal Republic of Germany," typescript, circa 1978 February (Folder 722: 10)
  - "The New Chairman of the Jusos, an 'Anti-Revisionist,'" Ladies' Garment Workers' Union General Executive Board, outline notes, 1978 February 9 (Folder 722: 11)
  - "Towards a Balanced Defense Strategy," holograph and typescript, 1978 February 9 (Folder 722: 13)
  - "Eurocommunism and the Present Crisis," typescript, 1978 March (Folder 722: 14)
  - "The Disarmament Conference of the Socialist International," typescript, circa 1978 April (Folder 722: 15)
  - "The Convention of the Austrian Socialist Party (SPÖ)," typescript, circa 1978 May (Folder 722: 16)
  - "The Eleventh DGB Congress and Related Issues," typescript, circa 1978 June (Folder 722: 17)
  - Draft speech for Sol C. Chaikin, holograph and typescript, 1978 June 6 (Folder 722: 18)
  - Tribute to Fritz G. A. Kraemer, holograph and typescript, 1978 July 21 (Folder 722: 19)
  - "Detente's Triple Threat," typescript, 1978 November 21 (Folder 722: 20)
  - "The Great Debate: Defense, SALT II," outline notes, circa 1979 (Folder 722: 21)
  - Report on international resolutions submitted to International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union convention, holograph, circa 1979 (Folder 722: 22)
  - Suggested corrections to David W. Lee, "The Soviet Merchant Marine: Economic and Strategic Challenge to the Western Alliance," holograph and typescript, 1979 (Folder 722: 23)
    Includes text of Atlantic Council study.
  - Suggested corrections to Gus Tyler, George Meany: The Making of a Freedom Fighter, holograph and typescript, 1979 (Folder 722: 24)
    Includes text of pamphlet.
  - "Iran: The Witches' Broth,", 1979 February 5
    - Notes and preliminary drafts (Folder 723: 1)
    - Final draft, typescript (Folder 723: 2)
  - Draft speech for Lane Kirkland at Drexel Institute, holograph and typescript, 1979 June 2 (Folder 723: 3)
  - Autobiographical notes, 1980s (Folder 723: 4)
  - "Detente: Its Why and Wherefore," typescript, 1980s (Folder 723: 5)
  - "International Situation," outline notes, 1980s (Folder 723: 6)
  - "Notes on Russia's Old New Right by Alexander Yanov," holograph and typescript, 1980s (Folder 723: 7)
  - Speech re communism, incomplete typed transcript, 1980s (Folder 723: 8)
  - "The German LaRouche Organization (EAP)," typescript, 1980s (Folder 723: 9)
  - "Poland 1980," (Folder 723: 10)
  - "Detente: Turmoil and Torment," holograph and typescript, 1980 February 8 (Folder 723: 11)
  - "Labor in 'Socialist' Societies: Blue Collar Workers in Eastern Europe,", 1980 May 14 (Folder 723: 12)
    Draft speech for Sol C. Chaikin at Conference on Labor in Socialist Societies, Stanford University. Agenda, holograph, and typescript.
  - Memorandum re Poland, holograph and typescript, circa 1980 September (Folder 723: 13)
  - Report on international resolutions submitted to International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union convention, 1980 September (Folder 723: 14)
  - Suggested corrections to "The Credibility of the NATO Deterrent" by unidentified author, holograph, circa 1980 September (Folder 723: 15)
    Includes text of study.
  - Draft letter to Lech Walesa and Anna Walentynowicz for Sol C. Chaikin, holograph and typescript, 1980 September 10 (Folder 723: 16)
  - "The Gdansk Charter: Lights On in Poland?," holograph and typescript, 1980 December 1 (Folder 723: 17)
  - "Two Internationals," typescript, 1980 December 16 (Folder 723: 18)
  - "The People Wonder Why," holograph and typescripts, 1980 December 18 (Folder 723: 19)
  - "The Campaign against the Stationing of NATO Medium-Range Missiles in West Germany," typescript, circa 1981 (Box-folder 724: 1)
  - "DGB President Vetter and the 'Peace Campaign,'" typescript, 1981 (Folder 724: 2)
  - Notes re Poland, circa 1981 (Folder 724: 3)
  - Message to International Conference in Honor of Andrei Sakharov, 1981 May (Folder 724: 4)
    Program, holograph, and typescript.
  - Notes re criticisms of American labor movement, circa 1981 May 31 (Folder 724: 5)
  - Draft speech for AFL-CIO representative at Trades Union Congress meeting, holograph and typescript, 1981 June (Folder 724: 6)
  - "West German Teachers' Union Supports 'Peace Campaign,'" typescript, circa 1981 October (Folder 724: 7)
  - "Bavaria against the 'Enemy States' Articles in the U.N. Charter," typescript, circa 1981 November (Folder 724: 8)
  - "Communist Infiltration of the DGB," typescript, 1981 December 12 (Folder 724: 9)
  - "Lights Out: From Kronstadt to Warsaw," holograph and typescript, 1981 December 31 (Folder 724: 10)
  - "America's World Responsibility," holograph and typescript, circa 1982 (Folder 724: 11)
  - "German Uncertainties," notes and typescript, circa 1982 (Folder 724: 12)
  - Notes re Germany, circa 1982 (Folder 724: 13)
  - Notes re Poland, circa 1982 (Folder 724: 14)
  - "[Heinz] Vetter's Successor," typescript, circa 1982 (Folder 724: 15)
  - Memorandum re Germany, typescript, 1982 February 26 (Folder 724: 16)
  - "Ernst Breit, Successor-Designate of DGB President H. O. Vetter," typescript, circa 1982 March (Folder 724: 17)
  - "The SPD Congress," typescript, circa 1982 April (Folder 724: 18)
  - "Lenin, Germany, and the Present Crisis," typed transcript, 1982 November 3 (Folder 724: 19)
    Speech, East-West Round Table, New York City.
  - Memorandum re Andrei Kistiakovsky, typescript, circa 1983 (Folder 724: 20)
  - "Scientists and AFL-CIO" (typescript), circa 1983 (Folder 724: 21)
  - "Historic Event at Arden House,", 1983 March 20 (Folder 724: 22)
    Speech, Arden House Conference on Science and Labor, Columbia University. Outline notes and program material.
  - "The American Bishops' Pastoral Letter on Atomic Arms and the Nuclear Debate in Germany," typescript, circa 1983 April (Folder 724: 23)
  - Speech, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union Committee on International Affairs meeting, outline notes, 1983 May 30 (Folder 724: 24)
  - Message to memorial service for Charles S. Zimmerman, holograph and typescript, 1983 June (Folder 724: 25)
  - "Some Proposals," holograph and typescript, 1983 July 22 (Folder 724: 26)
  - "In Reply to Mrs. Massie's Plea that We Should Realize that the Russians Are 'Human Beings,'" holograph, 1985 October (Folder 724: 27)
  - Notes and fragments (Folder 724: 28-30)
  - Notes and fragments (Box-folder 725: 1-3)
- OTHER UNPUBLISHED MATERIAL, 1926-1989 (Boxes 725-754)
  Third-party correspondence, writings by others, financial records, minutes, resolutions, memoranda, reports, and organizational internal documents and issuances, arranged by organization associated with their origin when possible, or, failing that, by individual author or topic.
  - Biographical data, 1954-1978 (Folder 725: 4)
    Biographical sketches, photocopy of memoir about Lovestone (apparently by David Dubinsky), and letters and press releases about Lovestone.
  - Personal documents, 1959-1988 (Folder 725: 5)
    Passport, appointment book, address books, certificates, and miscellany.
  - Personal financial papers
    Mainly receipts and bills.
    - 1939-1969 (Folder 725: 6)
    - 1971-1982 (Box-folder 726: 1)
    - 1983-1989 (Folder 726: 2)
  - AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations)
    - AFL-CIO Free Trade Union News audit reports, 1963-1973 (Folder 726: 3)
    - Third-party correspondence
      - 1955-1957 (Folder 726: 4)
      - 1958-1959 (Folder 726: 5)
      - 1960-1961 (Box-folder 727: 1)
      - 1962-1964 (Folder 727: 2)
      - 1965-1969 (Folder 727: 3)
      - 1970-1976 (Folder 727: 4)
      - 1977-1983 (Folder 727: 5)
    - Executive Council statements and resolutions
      - 1955-1959 (Folder 727: 6)
      - 1960-1963 (Folder 727: 7)
      - 1964-1969 (Box-folder 728: 1)
      - 1970-1979 (Folder 728: 2)
      - 1980-1982 (Folder 728: 3)
      - 1983-1985 (Folder 728: 4)
    - Internal documents
      - 1955-1956 (Folder 728: 5)
      - 1957-1958 (Folder 728: 6)
      - 1959 (Folder 728: 7)
      - 1960-1961 (Box-folder 729: 1)
      - 1963-1969 (Folder 729: 2)
      - 1970-1979 (Folder 729: 3)
      - 1980-1988 (Folder 729: 4)
    - International Affairs Department - Internal documents
      - 1960-1964 (Folder 729: 5)
      - 1965-1968 (Folder 729: 6)
      - 1970-1973 (Folder 729: 7)
      - 1974-1978 (Box-folder 730: 1)
      - 1980-1983 (Folder 730: 2)
    - Minutes, 1956-1958 (Folder 730: 3)
    - Public issuances
      - 1956-1959 (Folder 730: 4)
      - 1960-1969 (Folder 730: 5)
      - 1970-1979 (Folder 730: 6)
      - 1980-1985 (Folder 730: 7)
  - African-American Labor Center - Internal documents, 1978-1979 (Folder 730: 8)
  - Agency for International Development - Labor Advisory Committee - Internal documents, 1964 (Folder 730: 9)
  - American Federation of Labor (Box 731)
    - Third-party correspondence, 1945-1955 (Folder 731: 1)
    - Internal documents
      - 1943-1950 (Folder 731: 2)
      - 1951-1952 (Folder 731: 3)
      - 1953-1954 (Folder 731: 4)
      - 1955 (Folder 731: 5)
      - Undated (Folder 731: 6)
    - Minutes, 1952-1955 (Box-folder 732: 1)
    - Public issuances, 1946-1955 (Folder 732: 2)
  - American Institute for Free Labor Development - Internal documents, 1969-1982 (Folder 732: 3)
  - Atlantic Council - Issuances and internal documents
    - 1967-1977 (Folder 732: 4)
    - 1978 (Folder 732: 5)
    - 1979 (Folder 732: 6)
    - 1980 (Box-folder 733: 1)
    - 1981 (Folder 733: 2)
    - 1982 (Folder 733: 3)
    - 1983 (Folder 733: 4)
    - 1984 (Folder 733: 5)
    - 1985 (Folder 733: 6)
    - 1986 (Folder 733: 7)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 734: 1)
    - 1988-1989 (Folder 734: 2)
    - Undated (Folder 734: 3)
  - British-North American Committee - Issuances and internal documents, 1972-1979 (Folder 734: 4)
  - Canadian-American Assembly - Internal documents, 1964 (Folder 734: 5)
  - Center for Cuban Studies
    Internal documents (photocopies). Includes some related material re Cuba.
    - 1975-1978 (Folder 734: 6)
    - 1979-1983 (Folder 734: 7)
    - Undated (Box-folder 735: 1)
  - Committee for the Free World - Issuances, 1981 (Folder 735: 2)
  - Committee on the Present Danger - Issuances and internal documents
    - 1976-1979 (Folder 735: 3)
    - 1980-1983 (Folder 735: 4)
    - 1984 (Folder 735: 5)
    - 1985-1986 (Folder 735: 6)
    - 1987-1989 (Folder 735: 7)
  - Committee to Defend America/Citizens for Victory - Internal documents, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 736: 1)
  - Communist Party, U.S.A.
    - Third-party correspondence
      Mainly telegrams exchanged between Communist Party, U.S.A. delegation in Moscow and Communist Party, U.S.A. headquarters in New York.
      - 1926-1929 (Folder 736: 2)
      - Undated (1929) (Folder 736: 3)
    - Political Committee minutes (photocopies), 1925-1928 (Folder 736: 4)
  - Communist Party (Opposition)/Independent Labor League of America - Internal documents, 1934-1940 (Folder 736: 5)
    Includes typed transcript of Nikolai Bukharin, "The Fundamental Problems of Contemporary Culture", and syllabi of course on Marxism by Will Herberg.
  - Conference in Solidarity with the Liberation Struggles of the Peoples of Southern Africa, New York, 1981 (Folder 736: 6)
    Program and conference papers.
  - Conference of European Trade Union Centres - Issuances, 1972-1975 (Folder 736: 7)
  - Congress of Industrial Organizations - Internal documents, 1955 (Folder 736: 8)
  - Council on Foreign Relations - Issuances and internal documents
    - 1976-1981 (Folder 736: 9)
    - 1982-1986 (Folder 736: 10)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 737: 1)
    - 1988-1989 (Folder 737: 2)
  - Council on Islamic Affairs - Internal documents, 1958 (Folder 737: 3)
  - Dag Hammarskjöld Foundation - Internal documents, 1963 (Folder 737: 4)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee - Issuances, 1979-1981 (Folder 737: 5)
  - Deutscher Gewerkschaftsbund - Issuances and internal documents, 1971-1983 (Folder 737: 6)
  - East-West Round Table - Issuances and internal documents, 1982-1987 (Folder 737: 7)
  - Federación Interamericana de Trabajadores de la Industria Textil, Vestuario, Cuero y Calzado - Issuances and internal documents, 1976-1983 (Folder 737: 8)
  - Free Trade Union Committee
    - Audit reports, 1957-1958 (Folder 737: 9)
    - Bulletins
      - 1948-1949 (Folder 737: 10)
      - 1950-1952 (Folder 737: 11)
    - Financial records, 1950 (Folder 737: 12)
    - Minutes, 1946 (Folder 737: 13)
  - Friedrich Ebert Stiftung - Issuances and internal documents, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 738: 1)
  - George C. Marshall Foundation - Issuances, 1982-1987 (Folder 738: 2)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions
    - Issuances and internal documents
      - 1950-1954 (Folder 738: 3)
      - 1955 (Folder 738: 4)
      - 1956-1958 (Folder 738: 5)
      - 1959 (Folder 738: 6)
      - 1960-1961 (Folder 738: 7)
      - 1962-1964 (Folder 738: 8)
      - 1967 (Box-folder 739: 1)
      - 1968-1973 (Folder 739: 2)
      - 1974-1983 (Folder 739: 3)
    - World Congress, 4th, Vienna, 1955 (Folder 739: 4-5)
      Internal documents.
  - International Federation of Trade Unions - Minutes, 1945 (Folder 739: 6)
  - International Labor Organization - Internal documents, 1960-1961 (Folder 739: 7)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union - Issuances and internal documents (Box 740)
    - 1975-1984 (Folder 740: 1)
    - 1986 (Folder 740: 2)
  - Italian American Labor Council - Issuances, 1977-1982 (Folder 740: 3)
  - National Committee for a Free Europe - Internal documents, 1951-1952 (Folder 740: 4)
  - National Strategy Committee - Internal documents, 1962 (Folder 740: 5)
  - One University Place Tenants Association - Material re building in which Lovestone resided, 1974-1989 (Folder 740: 6)
  - Organizacién Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores - Issuances, 1963-1973 (Folder 740: 7)
  - Palestine Solidarity Committee - Internal documents (photocopies)
    - 1976-1979 (Folder 740: 8)
    - 1980-1982 (Folder 740: 9)
  - Social Democrats, U.S.A. - Issuances and internal documents, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 741: 1)
  - Socialist International
    - Congress, Vancouver, 1978 (Folder 741: 2)
    - Issuances and internal documents
      - 1951-1981 (Folder 741: 3)
      - 1982 (Folder 741: 4)
      - 1983 (Folder 741: 5)
  - Trades Union Congress - Issuances and internal documents (Box 742)
    - 1971-1973 (Folder 742: 1)
    - 1977-1980 (Folder 742: 2)
  - U.S. Labor Party/National Democratic Policy Committee - Issuances, 1976-1984 (Folder 742: 3)
    Includes related organizations.
  - United Automobile Workers Union - Issuances and internal documents, 1980-1983 (Folder 742: 4)
  - United States, Deptartment of Labor - Internal documents, 1961-1964 (Folder 742: 5)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions - Internal documents and issuances, 1945-1969 (Folder 742: 6)
  - Writings by others
    - Barton, Paul
      - "Fonctions des conventions collectives," typescript, 1950s (Folder 742: 7)
      - "Trade Unions behind the Iron Curtain," typescript, 1950s (Folder 742: 8)
      - "Current State of the International Labor Movement and the Choices Facing American Labor in the 70's," typescript, 1972 (Folder 742: 9)
    - Chudnovsky, David and Gregory - Writings, 1978 (Folder 742: 10)
      Includes material relating to efforts to secure permission for the Chudnovskys to emigrate from the Soviet Union.
    - Cuneo, Ernest L. (Box 743)
      - "Israel and the Follies of the Great Democracies," typescript, 1983 (Folder 743: 1)
      - Miscellaneous, typescripts, 1980s (Folder 743: 2)
    - Deverall, Richard L. G., "The Emergence of India in the Post-War-II Period as the Political Leader of Asia," typescript, 1949 (Folder 743: 3)
    - Greig, Ian, "The Ultra-Left Offensive against Multinational Companies," typescript, 1970s (Folder 743: 4)
    - Hayenko, Fedir S., "Soviet Trade Unions," typescript, 1960s (Folder 743: 5)
    - Kaelas, Aleksander, "From Capitalism to Bolshevism: The Worker in the Soviet," typescript, 1949 (Folder 743: 6)
    - Lang, Serge - Writings, 1980 (Folder 743: 7)
      Includes material assembled by Lang re federal funding of scientific research.
    - Lubkemeier, Eckhard, "Probleme, Voraussetzungen und Chancen einer Konventionalisierung der NATO-Strategie," typescript, 1983 (Folder 743: 8)
    - Malara, Jean, and Lucienne Rey, "Le syndicalisme polonais: Des ses débuts a l'heure presente," typescript, 1950s (Box-folder 744: 1)
    - Mihajlov, Mihajlo - Writings, 1971-1981 (Folder 744: 2)
      Includes material relating to Mihajlov.
    - Politicus, "The Last Chance of the Free: Coexistence on All Levels," typescript, 1970s (Folder 744: 3)
    - Schwarz, Salomon M., "Soviet Labor Policy," typescript, 1947 (Folder 744: 4-5)
    - Springer, Axel - Statements, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 745: 1)
      Includes press releases of Axel Springer Verlag.
    - Taft, Philip, "In Defense of Freedom: American Labor and Foreign Affairs," typescript, 1970s (Folder 745: 2-6)
    - Taft, Philip, "In Defense of Freedom" (Box-folder 746: 1)
    - Theimer, Walter, "The League of Forlorn Hope: A History of the German Uprising against Hitler on July 20th, 1944," typescript, 1980s (Folder 746: 2)
    - Toth, Janos, "The Case of Czechoslovakia: Occupation of Czechoslovakia and the Rule of Law," typescript, 1969 (Folder 746: 3)
    - Van Meer, Marcus, "Banks, Tanks, and Freedom: When Dollar Diplomacy Meets Police Communism, and What Is to Be Done," typescript, 1980s (Folder 746: 5)
  - Subject file
    Third-party correspondence, speeches and writings by others, reports, memoranda, statements, resolutions, bulletins, and circulars.
    - Africa, 1960-1978 (Folder 746: 5)
    - Algeria, 1958-1960 (Folder 746: 6)
    - Argentina, 1971 (Folder 746: 7)
    - Asia, 1951-1982 (Folder 746: 8)
    - Australia, 1954 (Folder 746: 9)
    - Brazil, 1966-1970 (Folder 746: 10)
    - Bulgaria, 1947-1950 (Folder 746: 11)
    - Chile, circa 1972 (Folder 746: 12)
    - China, 1945-1988 (Box-folder 747: 1)
    - Communism (International)
      - 1951-1961 (Folder 747: 2)
      - 1964-1965 (Folder 747: 3)
      - 1976-1980 (Folder 747: 4)
    - Communism—United States, 1939-1961 (Folder 747: 5)
    - Czechoslovakia, 1950-1978 (Folder 747: 6)
    - Defense (including Strategic Arms Limitation Talks), 1973-1985 (Box-folder 748: 1)
    - Energy (including oil), 1973-1983 (Folder 748: 2)
    - Espionage and intelligence operations, 1938-1980 (Folder 748: 3)
      Includes photocopy of Herbert Solow memorandum re Whittaker Chambers.
    - Estonia, 1946-1974 (Folder 748: 4)
    - Europe, 1950-1983 (Folder 748: 5)
    - Europe, Eastern, 1960-1980 (Folder 748: 6)
    - Finland, 1973 (Folder 748: 7)
    - Germany (Box 749)
      - 1930s-1963 (Folder 749: 1)
      - 1968-1976 (Folder 749: 2)
      - 1977-1983 (Folder 749: 3)
    - Great Britain, 1948-1981 (Folder 749: 4)
    - Greece, 1945-1964 (Folder 749: 5)
    - Hungary, 1951-1977 (Folder 749: 6)
    - India, 1954-1962 (Folder 749: 7)
    - Israel, 1964-1982 (Box-folder 750: 1)
    - Italy, 1973-1985 (Folder 750: 2)
    - Japan, 1967-1968 (Folder 750: 3)
    - Labor (International), 1947-1979 (Folder 750: 4)
    - Labor—United States, 1936-1987 (Folder 750: 5)
    - Latin America, 1960-1983 (Folder 750: 6)
    - Lebanon, 1982 (Folder 750: 7)
    - Lithuania, 1986 (Folder 750: 8)
    - Middle East, circa 1955-1981 (Folder 750: 9)
    - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1966-1989 (Box-folder 751: 1)
    - Poland, 1947-1984 (Folder 751: 2)
    - Romania, 1949-1977 (Folder 751: 3)
    - Soviet Union
      - 1948-1953 (Folder 751: 4)
      - 1955-1969 (Folder 751: 5)
      - 1970-1974 (Box-folder 752: 1)
      - 1975-1979 (Folder 752: 2)
      - 1980-1986 (Folder 752: 3)
      - Undated (Folder 752: 4)
    - Spain, 1950-1963 (Folder 752: 5)
    - Sweden, 1982-1983 (Folder 752: 6)
    - United Nations, 1950-1983 (Box-folder 753: 1)
    - United States—Economic conditions, 1959-1986 (Folder 753: 2)
    - United States—Foreign relations, 1949-1984 (Folder 753: 3)
    - United States—Politics and government
      - 1955-1972 (Folder 753: 4)
      - 1978-1985 (Folder 753: 5)
    - Vietnam, 1954-1982 (Folder 753: 6)
    - World politics, 1955-1986 (Folder 753: 7)
    - Yugoslavia, 1951-1982 (Folder 753: 8)
  - Miscellany (Box-folder 754: 1-2)
    Includes programs, resumés, notes, and fragments.